GETTING AUDIO TO LOOK GOOD
USUALLY MEANS BOUNCING BETWEEN PLAYERS,
PLUGINS, AND EXPORT TOOLS.
VISUALIZER KEEPS IT IN ONE
PLACE:
DROP IN A TRACK OR
OPEN THE MIC,
AND IT TURNS SOUND INTO
MOTION ACROSS SEVEN CANVAS2D MODES.
WHAT MAKES IT FEEL SOLID
IS THAT IT’S NOT JUST
REACTING TO VOLUME.
BEAT DETECTION TRACKS SPECTRAL FLUX,
THE BPM READOUT SETTLES INTO
SOMETHING USABLE,
AND THE STEM-BAND SLIDERS LET
YOU DECIDE WHETHER THE VISUALS
SHOULD FOLLOW THE SUB,
THE BASS,
OR THE BRIGHTER STUFF ON
TOP. SWAP BETWEEN EIGHT PALETTES AND
THE COLOUR SHIFTS EASE OVER
INSTEAD OF SNAPPING,
SO YOU CAN KEEP EXPLORING
WITHOUT BREAKING THE FLOW.
IF YOU’RE WORKING FROM FILES,
IT PULLS IN TITLE,
ARTIST, AND ALBUM ART AUTOMATICALLY.
IF YOU’RE PERFORMING LIVE,
THE MIC INPUT HAS ITS
OWN SENSITIVITY CONTROL.
AND WHEN SOMETHING FINALLY LANDS,
YOU CAN GRAB A PNG
OR KICK OUT A FIVE-SECOND
9:16 WEBM LOOP IN ONE
CLICK.
SO INSTEAD OF FIDDLING WITH
SETUP,
YOU GET A VISUAL THAT
ACTUALLY KEEPS UP WITH THE
SOUND AND IS READY TO
SHARE.